<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>My Daily Quotes</title>
    <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
    <description>A collection of daily inspirations.</description>

    <item>
      <title>Don’t get bitter, get better. - Tiger Woods</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Tiger Woods</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>There’s no way around hard work. Embrace it. You have to put in the hours because there is always something you can improve on. - Roger Federer</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Roger Federer</description>
    </item>  

    <item>
      <title>Gold medals aren’t really made of gold. They’re made of sweat, determination, and a hard-to-find alloy called guts. - Dan Gable</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Dan Gable</description>
    </item>  

    <item>
      <title>You miss 100% of the shots you don’t take” and “A good hockey player plays where the puck is. A great hockey player plays where the puck is going to be. - Wayne Gretzky</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Wayne Gretzky</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Pressure is something you feel when you don’t know what the hell you’re doing. - Peyton Manning</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Peyton Manning</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Pressure is a Privilege - Virgil van Dijk</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Virgil van Dijk</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Dreams are free. Goals have a cost. While you can daydream for free, goals don’t come without a price. Time, Effort, Sacrifice, and Sweat. How will you pay for your goals? - Usain Bolt</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Usain Bolt</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>I can only control my performance. If I do my best, then I can feel good at the end of the day. - Michael Phelps</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Michael Phelps</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Preparation is everything and focus is the key. It’s easy to say you gave it your all out on the pitch. But the point is if you’d prepared you’d have had more to give and you’ve played better. - Eric Cantona</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Eric Cantona</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The harder I work, the luckier I get. - Gary Player</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Gary Player</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Hard work beats talent when talent fails to work hard. - Kevin Durant</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Kevin Durant</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can’t accept not trying. - Michael Jordan</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Michael Jordan</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William Arthur Ward</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>William Arthur Ward</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>It’s not whether you get knocked down, it’s whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Vince Lombardi</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Sweat plus sacrifice equals success. - Charles Finley</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Charles Finley</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Today I will do what others won’t, so tomorrow I can do what others can’t. - Jerry Rice</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Jerry Rice</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person’s determination. - Tommy Lasorda</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Tommy Lasorda</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice, and most of all, love of what you are doing. - Pele</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Pele</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>There may be people who have more talent than you, but there’s no excuse for anyone to work harder than you do. - Derek Jeter</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Derek Jeter</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Talent is never enough. With few exceptions, the best players are the hardest workers. - Magic Johnson</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Magic Johnson</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Success is born out of faith, an undying passion, and a relentless drive. - Stephen Curry</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Stephen Curry</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>My confidence comes from the daily grind—training my butt off day in and day out. - Hope Solo</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Hope Solo</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The lessons of the sports field prepare you for the game of life. - John Wooden</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>John Wooden</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Sports teaches you character. It teaches you to play by the rules, it teaches you to know what it feels like to win and lose—it teaches you about life. - Billie Jean King</title>
      <link>https://dakboard.com</link>
      <description>Billie Jean King</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>


